So what else do we have?
We have elements, so when it comes to elements,
we can add to them on top of the other layers that we have.
And we can use them as well.
So again, inside the elements, we have the AI generator.
So we can use the AI to generate us logos, generate us stickers,
and generate us images that we can add on top of
these very layers that we have over here.
What else can we add?
We have lines to add, so these are the elements, right?
We have plenty of line styles by clicking on more for each of them.
I'll be able to access more and more of these.
So as you see, we have lines, we have arrows, we have shapes,
like rectangle, you know,
ellipse, triangle, or we have decoration.
So these are also available, these kind of stylish elements
that I can add to my project, whenever that I need them.
So as you see over here, we also have kind of pro options
that we cannot use.
We need to upgrade to the pro plan in order to use them.
We have dialogue, we have star, we have social media icons,
we have emojis, we have animals, as you see,
we have masks, we have sails, so sail badges,
like now, free, et cetera.
Cute, brush, banner, you know.
And as you see, there's endless elements.
And for example, if you're looking for elements
for a certain kind of purpose, all you need to do is
I need to come here and search for that very element.
So for example, I can say, I want crisp mess elements, right?
So I search, and afterwards, as you see,
the crisp mess elements will be loaded for me.
So if I wait a little bit, you'll see that, yep.
Plenty of them are pro, and some of them are free,
and all of them are edible to my project, whenever that I want,
on top of the other leaves.